<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DocReader-Authenticity</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="regula_document_reader">Regula Document Reader</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="select_scenario">Select Scenario</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>
    <string name="minus">—</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="application">Application</string>
    <string name="api">API</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="check">✔</string>
    <string name="string_default">default</string>
    <string name="stepper_value">%1$d %2$s</string>
    <string name="skip_rfid_button">Skip rfid button</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results">ResultsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_direct_results">DirectActivity</string>
    <string name="direct">Direct</string>
    <string name="overall_result">OVERALL_RESULT: </string>
    <string name="success_fail">success/fail</string>
    <string name="results">Results</string>
    <string name="compare">Compare</string>
    <string name="value">value</string>
    <string name="comparison_value">comparison value</string>
    <string name="rfid">RFID</string>
    <string name="auth">Auth</string>
    <string name="ic_menu_info_details">ic_menu_info_details</string>
    <string name="help_image">help image</string>
    <string name="authenticity_checks">Authenticity Checks</string>
    <string name="help_authenticity">The Document Reader SDK provides numerous checks, representing the advanced security techniques to verify the document`s authenticity and prevent its counterfeiting.</string>
    <string name="liveness_params">livenessParams</string>
    <string name="help_liveness">Document Liveness Check is a complex set of authenticity verifications, ensuring that the identity document is physically presented.</string>
    <string name="use_liveness">useLiveness</string>
    <string name="check_holo">checkHolo</string>
    <string name="check_ed">checkED</string>
    <string name="check_ovi">checkOVI</string>
    <string name="check_mli">checkMLI</string>
    <string name="check_dynaprint">checkMLI</string>
    <string name="check_black_and_white_copy">checkBWCopy</string>
    <string name="help_use_liveness">In active state allows you to set LivenessParams, in the inactive state cancels use LivenessParams</string>
    <string name="help_holo">In this check, the presence of holographic effect and the shape of hologram image are analyzed.</string>
    <string name="help_ovi">Optically Variable Ink objects change their color and appearance under different illumination conditions.</string>
    <string name="help_mli">Multiple Laser Images is the technology of secure printing, resulting in different graphics depending on the viewing angle.</string>
    <string name="help_ed">In this check, the image, captured by the device`s camera from the computer`s monitor or other external display, is validated.</string>
    <string name="help_dynaprint">dopolnit` opisanie.</string>
    <string name="help_black_and_white_copy">dopolnit` opisanie.</string>
    <string name="check_image_patterns">checkImagePatterns</string>
    <string name="help_check_image_patterns">Many personal documents have the laminated layer with unique image patterns, standing out by their shape, size, and color.</string>
    <string name="check_photo_embedding">checkPhotoEmbedding</string>
    <string name="help_check_photo_embedding">This check controls the type of embedding the photo (affixed or printed) in the document of concrete type according to the template from the database.</string>
    <string name="check_barcode_format">checkBarcodeFormat</string>
    <string name="help_check_barcode_format">In this check, the number and type of barcodes for the secure document are validated, together with their structure and encoded data.</string>
    <string name="check_photo_comparison">checkPhotoComparison</string>
    <string name="help_check_photo_comparison">This check compares the photo extracted from the document data page in white light with the portrait from another source. The photos are compared with the help of Regula Face SDK.</string>
    <string name="check_uv_luminiscence">checkUVLuminiscence</string>
    <string name="help_check_uv_luminiscence">The security documents are mostly printed on UV dull paper and must not fluoresce under ultraviolet light. Additionally, the verification reveals suspicious unevenness of the materials.</string>
    <string name="check_fibers">checkFibers</string>
    <string name="help_check_fibers">Document`s security paper may contain specific flexible fibers in its mixture. Their size, shape, and luminescent properties under UV lighting can be assessed.</string>
    <string name="check_ext_mrz">checkExtMRZ</string>
    <string name="help_check_ext_mrz">This check verifies the size of MRZ lines, their relative position, clues of possible alteration, etc.</string>
    <string name="check_ext_ocr">checkExtOCR</string>
    <string name="help_check_ext_ocr">This check controls the quality of personal data printing and positioning.</string>
    <string name="check_ir_b_900">checkIRB900</string>
    <string name="check_ir_visibility">checkIRVisibility</string>
    <string name="help_check_ir_visibility">This check validates the visibility of different elements (especially photo and images) under infrared light and compares to their representations in visible light.</string>
    <string name="check_ipi">checkIPI</string>
    <string name="help_check_ipi">This check visualizes the Invisible Personal Information, applied to the holder`s photo. In most cases, the hidden data is the document number or the holder`s first and last name.</string>
    <string name="check_axial">checkAxial</string>
    <string name="help_check_axial">This check detects the areas of the laminate film unevenness by applying the illumination scheme with coinciding angles of illumination and observation under visible white light.</string>
    <string name="check_letter_screen">checkLetterScreen</string>
    <string name="help_check_letter_screen">Some documents have the secondary (ghost) portrait formed by the wavy lines of the personal data, according to the LetterScreen++ technology.</string>
    <string name="mrz">MRZ</string>
    <string name="help_mrz">The Machine Readable Zone (MRZ) provides a set of essential data elements in a format, standardized for each type of a Machine Readable Travel Document (MRTD), that can be used by all receiving States regardless of their national script or customs. The data in the MRZ are formatted in such a way as to be readable by machines with standard capability worldwide.</string>
    <string name="viz">VIZ</string>
    <string name="help_viz">The Visual Inspection Zone (VIZ) of a Machine Readable Travel Document (MRTD) comprises the mandatory and optional data elements designed for visual inspection.</string>
    <string name="barcode">Barcode</string>
    <string name="help_barcode">Barcode is a means of storing data as a pattern of lines or dots.</string>
    <string name="add_parameter">Add parameter</string>
    <string name="result">Result:</string>
    <string name="code_definition">Code definition:</string>
    <string name="all_results">All Results</string>
    <string name="pageIndex">Page: %1$d</string>
    <string name="scenarios_warning">Unable to reproduce functionality without any scenarios - available scenarios list is empty</string>
    <string name="scenario_warning">Unable to reproduce functionality without FullAuth scenario installed - scenario not found</string>
    <string name="scan_mode_warning">select the method of document recognition - using the camera or gallery</string>
    <string name="strResetAllSettings">Reset all settings</string>
    <string name="strResetAllAppSettingsConfirmation">This will reset all settings of the application</string>
    <string name="strResetAllAPISettingsConfirmation">This will reset all API settings</string>
    <string name="strCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="strSendRequest">Send Request</string>
    <string name="strSelectImage">Select image</string>
    <string-array name="select_image">
        <item>Gallery</item>
        <item>Camera Shot</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>